Guide to the Victor F. Germack and Lori Shepard Germack Collection of Photographs of Indians of North America
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Card Photographs, 1863-circa 1910; Series II; 1.67; (3 boxes)
  - Other Card Photographs
    - Martin, Alexander
      - Sheltered Falls on the Pikes Peak Trail, Colorado (No. 1051), circa 1890 (Box 3, Folder 294)
    - McKay, William H.
      - Camp of Oglala Sioux Indian Soldiers and Squaw Laundresses at Fort Omaha, Nebraska, 1893-1894 (Box 20, Folder 295)
      - Oglala Sioux Indian Company I, Second United States Infantry, at Fort Omaha, Nebraska, 1893-1894 (Box 20, Folder 296)
    - Stotz, Christopher Charles
      - Exterior Portrait of Nine American Indian Men, Cheyenne Indians and Arapaho Indians, at Fort Reno, Indian Territory, 1877-1878 (Box 20, Folder 297)
        Identified individuals include Bear Louse, Big Horse (Cheyenne Indian), Bull Bear (Cheyenne Indian), Cheyenne Indian), Little Wolf (Ohkom Kakit, Magpie (Cheyenne Indian), Soft Belly (Hicks), Spring Water, Three Fingers (Cheyenne Indian), and Yellow Bear (Arapaho Indian)
    - Unidentified Photographers
      - Studio Portrait of Washakie, a Flathead Indian and Chief of the Shoshoni Indians, with Frederick Cook, Assistant Treasurer of the Overland Mail Company, circa 1860 (Box 3, Folder 298)
      - Hunting Party of European American Men and an American Indian Guide, circa 1890 (Box 3, Folder 299)
      - Lodge Interior with an American Indian Group, circa 1890; (2 photographic prints; 1 boudoir photograph) (Box 3, Folder 300-301)
      - Shohola Glen, Pennsylvania, circa 1890; (5 photographic prints) (Box 3, Folder 302-305)
      - Group of American Indian Men, Women, and Children, as well as European American Men at the Chapleau Subpost of the Hudson Bay Company, Chapleau, Ontario, 1884-1889; (1 panel photograph) (Box 3, Folder 306)
- Stereographs, circa 1860-circa 1925; Series III; 3; (3 boxes)
  Stereographs are double photographic prints that depict the same image taken from two slightly different perspectives and mounted on cards. Viewing the two-dimensional images through a stereoscope creates the illusion of a three-dimensional image to the viewer.
  Series III is arranged alphabetically by photographer or publisher followed by stereographs created by unidentified creators.
  Entries for individual stereographs include their titles, numbers on the mounts, and their series. The entries also document if no numbers or series information exists.
  Discrete groups of entries for stereographs published by Truman Ward Ingersoll and the Keystone View Company are arranged by series when known. Stereographs by these photographers without an identified series are arranged by their titles and numbers.
  Occasionally, to clarify the image content of particular stereographs, entries may include descriptions of the images.
  Associated Materials: A stereograph transparency can be found in Series VI. Photographic Transparencies.
  - American Stereoscopic Co.
    - Indian Chief (Paul Tahourhenche) and Daughter, Lorette, Quebec (No. 132), American Scenery, Vicinity of Quebec, circa 1870 (Box 4, Folder 307)
  - American Views
    - Crow Indian Warriors (No Number), Unidentified Series; Nine Crow Indian Men, circa 1890 (Box 4, Folder 308)
  - Angell, Clark L.
    - American Indians and European American Men Adjacent to Tipis (No Number), Unidentified Series, 1880-1881 (Box 4, Folder 309)
  - Barker, George
    - Pappoose in Indian Cradle, Goat Island, Niagara (No. 505), Niagara Falls, New York, circa 1875 (Box 4, Folder 310-311)
      Includes one clipped stereograph half.
    - Squaw and Pappoose (No. 571), Unidentified Series; Depicts a Tuscarora Indian Woman with a Child in a Cradleboard, circa 1875 (Box 4, Folder 312)
  - Beaman, Elias Olcott
    - Camp at Green River City (No. 1), U.S. Topographical and Geological Survey of the Valley of the Colorado, by J.W. Powell and A.H. Thompson, 1871 (Box 4, Folder 313)
    - Tuba and his Band on the Moincoppee (No. 69), Views in the Canons of the Colorado River and Among the Aztec Cities of Arizona, 1871 (Box 4, Folder 314)
      Published by E. & H. T. Anthony
    - Red Cañon, 3 miles Below Bee Hive Point Looking Down, (No. 15), Red Cañon, U.S. Topographical and Geological Survey of the Valley of the Colorado River of the West, 1871 (Box 4, Folder 314a)
    - Echo Park (No. 62), Echo Park, U.S. Topographical and Geological Survey of the Valley of the Colorado River of the West, 1871 (Box 4, Folder 314b)
    - Cottonwood Tree (No Number), Cataract Cañon, U.S. Topographical and Geological Survey of the Valley of the Colorado River of the West, 1871 (Box 4, Folder 315)
    - Eagle Cliff, (No Number), Cañon of Desolation, U.S. Topographical and Geological Survey of the Valley of the Colorado River of the West, 1871 (Box 4, Folder 315a)
    - Outer Walls of Mouqui, Showing Entrance and Ladders by Which People Ascend to Their Houses (No. 1907), California and Colorado, 1871 (Box 4, Folder 316)
  - Bell, William
    - The Northern Wall of the Grand Cañon of the Colorado, Near the Foot of To-Ro-Weap Valley (No. 14), Geographical Explorations and Surveys West of 100th Meridian, Expedition of 1873 (Box 4, Folder 317)
  - Bennett & Brown
    Bennett & Brown was a partnership between George C. Bennett and William Henry Brown in Santa Fe, New Mexico, 1880-1881.
    - Santa Fe and Vicinity, View from the Loma, Showing Central Part of City (No. 9), Among the Ancient and Interesting Scenery of New Mexico, circa 1880 (Box 4, Folder 318)
    - San Miguel Chapel, 300 Years Old (No. 12), Santa Fe and Vicinity, circa 1880 (Box 4, Folder 319)
    - San Miguel College and Chapel (No. 42), Santa Fe and Vicinity, circa 1880 (Box 4, Folder 320)
    - View From Old Fort Marcy Showing Central Part of City (No. 45), Santa Fe and Vicinity, circa 1880 (Box 4, Folder 321)
    - The Plaza, from Military Headquarters (No. 53), Santa Fe and Vicinity, circa 1880 (Box 4, Folder 322)
  - Bennett, Henry Hamilton
    - Ma-co-nu-gah and Big Bear (No. 276), Wanderings Among the Wonders and Beauties of Wisconsin Scenery, Among the Winnebagoes, circa 1875 (Box 4, Folder 323)
    - He-Noo-Ke-Ku (Youngest Girl) (No. 482), Wanderings Among the Wonders and Beauties of Wisconsin Scenery, Among the Winnebagoes, circa 1875 (Box 4, Folder 324)
  - Bradley, Bryant
    - Indian Tents, Bar Harbor, Mount Desert, Maine (No.149), Unidentified Series, circa 1872 (Box 4, Folder 325)
  - Brown, William Henry
    Associated Materials: Stereographs by William Henry Brown can also be found under the heading Bennett & Brown.
    - Interior of San Miguel Church (No. 11), Unidentified Series, circa 1881-1883 (Box 4, Folder 326)
    - San Miguel Chapel, 300 Years Old (No. 13), Santa Fe and Vicinity, circa 1881-1883 (Box 4, Folder 327)
    - Rear View of San Miguel Church (No. 16), Unidentified Series, circa 1881-1883 (Box 4, Folder 328)
    - San Miguel Chapel, Rear View, and Oldest House in City (No. 16), Santa Fe and Vicinity, circa 1881-1883 (Box 4, Folder 329)
    - Oldest House in Santa Fe (No. 18), Santa Fe and Vicinity, circa 1881-1883 (Box 4, Folder 330)
    - Indian Pottery (No. 25), Santa Fe and Vicinity, circa 1881-1883 (Box 4, Folder 331)
    - Bird's Eye View North from College (No. 30), Santa Fe and Vicinity, circa 1881-1883 (Box 4, Folder 332)
    - Santa Guadalupe Church, From River, 250 Years Old (No. 37), Santa Fe and Vicinity, circa 1881-1883 (Box 4, Folder 333)
    - Dos Cargas, Manner in Which Fuel is Brought to Santa Fe (No. 43), Santa Fe and Vicinity, circa 1881-1883 (Box 4, Folder 334)
    - Western Part of City from Old Fort Marcy (No. 46), Santa Fe and Vicinity, circa 1881-1883 (Box 4, Folder 335)
    - The Church (No. 82), Pueblo Tesuque Series, circa 1881-1883 (Box 4, Folder 336)
  - Calfee, Henry Bird
    - Studio Portrait of Three American Indian Men (No. Number), The Enchanted Land, or Wonders of the Yellowstone National Park, circa 1874 (Box 4, Folder 337)
  - Carbutt, John
    - Group of Mounted Pawnee Warriors (No. 203), Union Pacific Rail Road, Excursion to the 100th Meridian, October, 1866., 1866 October (Box 4, Folder 338)
    - Group of Indian Chiefs, Pawnee Tribe (No. 308), Views of the Rocky Mountains and Vicinity, 1866 October (Box 4, Folder 339)
      Seated from left to right is Sky Chief and Man Chief; Curly Chief is standing third from right.
  - Carter, Charles William
    - Pahute Indians, the Three Beauties (No. 97), Carter's Celebrated Indian Stereos; Three Paiute Indian Boys, circa 1867 (Box 4, Folder 340)
    - Pahute Jim (No Number), Carter's Celebrated Indian Stereos, circa 1867 (Box 4, Folder 341)
    - Snake (No Number), Carter's Celebrated Indian Stereos, circa 1867 (Box 4, Folder 342)
  - Caswell & Davy
    Partnership between William Caswell and William H. Davy in Duluth, Minnesota.
    - Chippewa Indians (No Number), Scenery on the Northern Pacific Railroad, circa 1870-1875 (Box 4, Folder 343)
  - Centennial Photographic Company
    - Two American Indian Men Carrying Two European American Men on their Backs Across a River (No. 60), International Exhibition, 1876 (Box 4, Folder 344)
  - Childs, Bernard Freemont
    - Indian Burial Ground, L'Anse (No. 73), Gems of Lake Superior Scenery, circa 1870 (Box 4, Folder 345)
      Published by Christ B. Brubaker, Houghton, Michigan.
  - Continent Stereoscopic Company
    - The Indian Pueblo of La Guna, New Mexico (No Number), Descriptive Views of the American Continent, circa 1880 (Box 4, Folder 346)
  - Curtis, George E.
    - Pappoose in Cradle (No. 334), Niagara Falls, New York, circa 1875 (Box 4, Folder 347)
  - Doerr, Henry A.
    - Interior of Mission San José y San Miguel de Aguayo, San Antonio, Texas (No Number), Unidentified Series, circa 1885 (Box 4, Folder 348)
  - E. & H. T. Anthony & Co.
    - Niagara Falls, Winter, Near Goat Island Bridge (No Number), Unidentified Series; Shows the Six Nation Indian Store, circa 1870 (Box 4, Folder 349)
      Distributed by W. D. Fenno & Son, Worcester, Massachusetts.
  - Fennemore, James
    - One of the Glens (No. 162), Glen Cañon, U.S. Topographical and Geological Survey of the Valley of the Colorado River of the West, 1872 (Box 4, Folder 349a)
  - Florida Club (Cooperative)
    The Florida Club was a cooperative venture formed by photographers Charles Seaver and George Pierron in 1874.
    - A Picture of the Indian Cut-Throats and Scalpers (No Number), Florida, The Land of Flowers and Tropical Scenery; Depicts Eagle Head (Minimic) and His Son, Howling Wolf (Ho-Na-Nist-To), Cheyenne Indians, at Fort Marion in Saint Augustine, Florida, 1874-1878 (Box 4, Folder 350)
    - Cheyenne Indian Prisoners at Fort Marion, Florida (No Number), Unidentified Series, 1875 (Box 4, Folder 351)
      Identified from left to right: wife of Black Horse, wife of Medicine Water, Black Horse, Medicine Water, and Menimic.
    - Kiowa Prisoners Arriving at Fort Marion, Florida (No Number), Unidentified Series, 1875 (Box 4, Folder 352)
      Published by W. H. Cushing, Palatka, Florida.
      Lone Wolf the Elder (Gui-pah-gho or Guipago) is seated in the second row, fourth from the right
    - American Indians in Uniform at Fort Marion, Florida (No Number), Unidentified Series, circa 1875 (Box 4, Folder 353)
    - Pyramids of Major Francis Langhorne Dade and 107 of his Men, who were Massacred at Fort Dade, Florida, by Osceola and his Band (No Number), Unidentified Series, circa 1885 (Box 4, Folder 354)
      Published by I. D. Israel.
  - Forsyth, Norman A.
    - Sun Worshippers, Preparing for Sun Dance (No. 6A), Unidentified Series, circa 1907-1909 (Box 4, Folder 355)
    - A Short Rest at the Choosing Dance (No. 11A), Unidentified Series, circa 1907-1909 (Box 4, Folder 356)
    - Mr. Wild Gun and Family (Blackfeet) (No. 13a), Unidentified Series, circa 1907-1909 (Box 4, Folder 357)
    - Sleep, My Baby, Sleep, Flathead Reservation (No. 19A), Unidentified Series, circa 1907-1909 (Box 4, Folder 358)
    - Chief Moise in Snake Dance (No. 20a), Unidentified Series, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 359)
    - Kootenais Raising Sun Dance Lodge (No. 29A), Unidentified Series, circa 1907-1909 (Box 4, Folder 360)
    - Painted Lodges of the Blackfeet (No Number), Unidentified Series, circa 1907-1909 (Box 4, Folder 361)
    - Valuable Elk Teeth Dresses of the Crows (No Number), Unidentified Series, circa 1907-1909 (Box 4, Folder 362)
  - Gaylord, Paul B.
    - Chippewa Indians (No Number), Scenery at the Head of Lake Superiors, circa 1882-1887 (Box 4, Folder 363)
  - H. C. White Company
    - Harvey's Famous Indian Store, Albuquerque, New Mexico, U.S.A. (No. 12276), Unidentified Series, 1906 (Box 4, Folder 364)
  - Hamilton & Hoyt
    Partnership of James H. Hamilton and Charles Franklin Hoyt in Sioux City, Iowa.
    - Mad Bear and Stormy Goose (Standing), Iron Horn and Sitting Crow (sitting), Sioux Chiefs (No Number), Unidentified Series, circa 1872 (Box 4, Folder 365)
  - Hamilton & Kodylek
    Partnership of James H. Hamilton and John Kodylek in Sioux City, Iowa.
    - Indian Tent, Group of Indians in Front (No. 104), Photographic Illustrations of Indian Character, Omaha Indians, circa 1872 (Box 4, Folder 366)
  - Hamilton, James H.
    - Touch the Clouds (Mahpíya Ičáhtagya or Mahpíya Íyapat'o), Sioux Chief (No. 129), Stereoscopic Views of the Northwest, 1877 (Box 4, Folder 367)
    - Omaha Council (No. 7), Stereoscopic Views of the Northwest, circa 1880 (Box 4, Folder 368)
    - Squaw with a Board (No. 50), Stereoscopic Views of the Northwest, Winnebago Indians, circa 1880 (Box 4, Folder 369)
    - Medicine Bear, Sioux Chief (No. 73 and No. 209), Stereoscopic Views of the Northwest, circa 1880 (Box 4, Folder 370)
    - Black Hawk, Sioux Chief (No. 101 and No. 205), Unidentified Series, circa 1880 (Box 4, Folder 371)
    - Roman Nose, Sioux Chief (No. 116), Unidentified Series, circa 1880 (Box 4, Folder 372)
    - Pretty Bear, Sioux Chief (No. 122 and No. 268), Unidentified Series, circa 1880 (Box 4, Folder 373)
    - Four Bears, Sioux Chief (No. 141 and No. 216), Unidentified Series, circa 1880 (Box 4, Folder 374)
    - Pawnee Chief (No. 168 and No. 518), Unidentified Series, circa 1880 (Box 4, Folder 375)
    - Red Dog, Sioux Chief (No Number), Unidentified Series, circa 1880 (Box 4, Folder 376)
    - Two Strike, Sioux Chief (No Number), Unidentified Series, circa 1880 (Box 4, Folder 377)
    - Sioux Chief (No Number), Stereoscopic Views of the Northwest, circa 1880 (Box 4, Folder 378)
    - Sioux Warrior (No Number), Stereoscopic Views of the Northwest, circa 1880 (Box 4, Folder 379)
  - Hillers, John Karl
    - Ú-Wa on a Rock (No. 6), U.S. Topographical and Geological Survey of the Valley of the Colorado River of the West, 1873 (Box 4, Folder 380)
      Published by John F. Jarvis, Washington, D.C.
    - The Basket Maker (No. 13), U.S. Topographical and Geological Survey of the Valley of the Colorado River of the West, 1873 (Box 4, Folder 381)
    - Game of Wolf and Deer (No. 19), U.S. Topographical and Geological Survey of the Valley of the Colorado River of the West, 1873 (Box 4, Folder 382)
    - Ań-Ti-Naints, Pu-Tú-Siv, and Wí-Chuts (No. 62), U.S. Topographical and Geological Survey of the Valley of the Colorado River of the West, 1873 (Box 4, Folder 383)
    - The Old Gamblers (No. 71), U.S. Topographical and Geological Survey of the Valley of the Colorado River of the West, 1873 (Box 4, Folder 384)
      Published by William B. Holmes.
    - Ká-Ni, Sleeping (No. 73), U.S. Topographical and Geological Survey of the Valley of the Colorado River of the West, 1873 (Box 4, Folder 385)
    - Ragged Walls, or Tantalus Creek (No. 195), U.S. Topographical and Geological Survey of the Valley of the Colorado River of the West, 1873 (Box 4, Folder 386)
    - A Dangerous Rapid, (No. 195), Grand Cañon of Colorado, U.S. Topographical and Geological Survey of the Valley of the Colorado River of the West, 1873 (Box 4, Folder 386a)
      Shows the Sockdolager Rapid of the Colorado River
    - Narrow Canyon with Water (No Number), U.S. Topographical and Geological Survey of the Valley of the Colorado River of the West, 1873 (Box 4, Folder 387)
    - Women of the Kai-vav-its Tribe Grinding (No Number), U.S. Topographical and Geological Survey of the Valley of the Colorado River of the West, 1873 (Box 4, Folder 388)
    - Ú-Wa, wife of Chu-Ar'-Ru-Um-Peak (No Number), U.S. Topographical and Geological Survey of the Valley of the Colorado River of the West, 1873 (Box 4, Folder 389)
    - Boulders (No Number), Glen Cañon, U.S. Topographical and Geological Survey of the Valley of the Colorado River of the West, 1873 (Box 4, Folder 390)
    - Boulder and Pool of Water (No Number), Glen Cañon, U.S. Topographical and Geological Survey of the Valley of the Colorado River of the West, 1873 (Box 4, Folder 391)
    - Blocks of Marble (No Number), Kanab Cañon, U.S. Topographical and Geological Survey of the Valley of the Colorado River of the West, 1870 (Box 4, Folder 391a)
    - Cañon (No Number), U.S. Topographical and Geological Survey of the Valley of the Colorado River of the West, 1873 (Box 4, Folder 391b)
    - Canyon with Water in Shadow and Beach in Foreground (No Number), Unidentified Series, 1873 (Box 4, Folder 392)
    - Ku-Ra-Tu, Paiute Indian Woman (No Number), Unidentified Series, 1873 (Box 4, Folder 393)
  - Hoard & Tenney
    Partnership between E. Harry Hoard and Charles A. Tenney in Winona, Minnesota.
    - Otter Tail Indians (No Number), Views on the Chippewa Reservation, White Earth, Minnesota, circa 1875-1883 (Box 4, Folder 394)
    - Indian Office at White Earth Minnesota, Paying an Indian for Work (No Number), Views on the Chippewa Reservation, White Earth, Minnesota, circa 1875-1883 (Box 4, Folder 395)
  - Ingersoll, Truman Ward
    This group of stereographs by Ingersoll include chromolithograph reproductions of photographs and represents part of an unidentified series.
    - Chippewa Squaw and Papoose (No. 404), circa 1898 (Box 4, Folder 396)
    - Chippewa Squaw Making Birch Canoe (No. 406), circa 1898-1900 (Box 4, Folder 397)
    - Family Group of Sioux and Lodge (No. 424), 1899 (Box 4, Folder 398)
    - Beef Issue to Sioux Indians at Standing Rock (No. 430), circa 1898-1900 (Box 4, Folder 399)
    - Gray Eagle and Family, Sioux Lodges (No. 436), 1899 (Box 4, Folder 400)
    - Passing the Peace Pipe Around the Council (No. 443), 1899 (Box 4, Folder 401)
    - Chippewa Squaws Braiding Rush Mats (No. 445), circa 1898-1900 (Box 4, Folder 402)
    - Chief Black Hawk, Squaw Papoose (No. 449), 1898 (Box 4, Folder 403)
    - Sioux Indian Rider and his Racing Pony (No. 454), circa 1898-1900 (Box 4, Folder 404)
    - The Old Chief, The Beaver's Camp (No. 460), circa 1898-1900 (Box 4, Folder 405-406)
    - Group of Black Foot Braves in Full Feather (No. 466), 1898 (Box 4, Folder 407)
    - Mounted Sioux and Camp (No. 472), 1899 (Box 4, Folder 408)
    - Sioux Indian Rider Making Good Medicine Before the Race (No. 475), circa 1898-1900 (Box 4, Folder 409)
    - Blackfoot Squaw's Papoose at Home (No. 486), 1898 (Box 4, Folder 410)
    - Jake Nahnami. Old Sioux Chief. (Walking Stones) and Jukawcauh Disca (No. 493), circa 1898-1900 (Box 4, Folder 411)
    - Drying Fish Meat in a Sioux Camp (No. 495), circa 1898-1900 (Box 4, Folder 412)
    - Gray Eagle and His Lodge (No. 496), 1899 (Box 4, Folder 413)
  - Illingworth, William H.
    - Iron Bear, Chief of Rees (Arikara Indians), Fort Berthold (No. 249), Crossing the Plains to Montana with Captain Fisk's Expedition, 1866 (Box 4, Folder 414)
      Published by John Carbutt, Chicago, Illinois.
    - Chief of the Gros Ventres (No. 250), Crossing the Plains to Montana with Captain Fisk's Expedition, 1866 (Box 4, Folder 415)
    - Indian Chiefs and Squaw, at Ft. Union (No. 256), Crossing the Plains to Montana with Captain Fisk's Expedition, 1866 (Box 4, Folder 416)
    - Old Betz or Old Bets (Hazainyankewin, Woman Who Runs for Huckleberries) (No Number), Unidentified Series; Depicts an Elderly Dakota Santee Indian Woman, 1868 (Box 4, Folder 417)
    - Sioux Indians (No Number), Unidentified Series; Two Dakota Indian Men, circa 1874-1880 (Box 4, Folder 418)
  - Jackson, William Henry
    - Otoe Indians (No. 202), Photographs of Indians, circa 1868 (Box 4, Folder 419)
    - Tunnel No. 4, Weber Canon (No. 37), Scenery of the Union Pacific Railroad, 1869-1872 (Box 4, Folder 420)
    - The Great Eastern, Echo Canon (No. 107), Scenery of the Union Pacific Railroad, 1869-1872 (Box 4, Folder 421)
    - Echo Canon, Looking Down (No. 109), Scenery of the Union Pacific Railroad, 1869-1872 (Box 4, Folder 422)
    - The Amphitheatre, Echo Canon (No. 125), Scenery of the Union Pacific Railroad, 1869-1872 (Box 4, Folder 423)
    - Castle Rock, Echo Canon (No. 128), Scenery of the Union Pacific Railroad, 1869-1872 (Box 4, Folder 424)
    - Rocks on Crow Creek, Near Sherman (No. 166), Scenery of the Union Pacific Railroad, 1869-1872 (Box 4, Folder 425)
    - View on the Upper Fire Hole River (No. 545), Yellowstone National Park, Hot Springs and Geysers, Department of the Interior, U.S. Geological Survey of the Territories, circa 1871 (Box 4, Folder 426)
    - Old Faithful in Eruption (No. 547), Yellowstone National Park, Hot Springs and Geysers, Department of the Interior, U.S. Geological Survey of the Territories, circa 1871 (Box 4, Folder 427)
    - Hot Springs Basin, Upper Fire Hole (No. 560), Yellowstone National Park, Hot Springs and Geysers, Department of the Interior, U.S. Geological Survey of the Territories, circa 1871 (Box 4, Folder 428)
    - Hot Springs Basin, Upper Fire Hole (No. 561), Yellowstone National Park, Hot Springs and Geysers, Department of the Interior, U.S. Geological Survey of the Territories, circa 1871 (Box 4, Folder 429)
    - Lower Basins (No. 567), Yellowstone National Park, Hot Springs and Geysers, Department of the Interior, U.S. Geological Survey of the Territories, circa 1871 (Box 4, Folder 430)
    - Packing and Sinching (No. 3507), Unidentified Series, circa 1871 (Box 4, Folder 431)
    - Bannock Indian Group Near Tipi and Windscreen (No Number), Unidentified Series, 1872 (Box 4, Folder 432)
    - Piah (Peter Snow) and Other Ute Chiefs (No. 4101), Unidentified Series, circa 1877-1878 (Box 4, Folder 433)
    - Ute Teepees (No. 4104), Unidentified Series, circa 1877-1878 (Box 4, Folder 434)
      Distributed by Walter V. Hayt, Santa Fe, New Mexico.
    - Echo Rock, Glen Eyrie (No. 520), Garden of the Gods and Monument Park, circa 1879- 1881 (Box 4, Folder 435)
  - Keystone View Company
    From 1892 to 1963, the Keystone View Company produced and distributed stereographs and lantern slides for educational institutions and the public from its headquarters in Meadville, Pennsylvania.
    Organized into two groups: "I" Series and Unidentified Series
    Stereograph cards produced by the Keystone View Company often include several numbers printed on their mounts that document the image. The numbers that appear in the upper center of the stereograph document the position of that card within a particular set.
    Additional numbers on the recto or verso of the card designate the negative number for the pair of images.
    Numbers with a "P" prefix designate the card as part of an educational set designed for elementary school age children.
    This group includes examples of images originally created for companies that the Keystone View Company acquired later.
    Numbers with a "W" prefix were images originally created or copyrighted by the H. C. White Company, which sold its stereographic stock and rights to the Keystone View Company in 1915.
    Numbers with a "V" prefix were images originally created or copyrighted by the Underwood & Underwood Company, which sold its stereographic stock and rights to the Keystone View Company in 1920.
    - "I" Series